{
    "subject": "resource/CCTV_New_Year's_Gala",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:New_Year's_television_specials",
    "human_readable": "The subject of CCTV New Year's Gala is Category:New_Year's_television_specials.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8727424740791321,
            "question": "What type of program is the CCTV New Year's Gala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8530437350273132,
            "question": "Who typically watches the CCTV New Year's Gala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8162338137626648,
            "question": "Is the CCTV New Year's Gala a traditional event?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8104071617126465,
            "question": "What kind of programming might be featured in the CCTV New Year's Gala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8037624955177307,
            "question": "During what holiday is the CCTV New Year's Gala broadcast?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7947059869766235,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in the CCTV New Year's Gala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.771916925907135,
            "question": "Why is the CCTV New Year's Gala popular?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7637156248092651,
            "question": "What is the historical context of the CCTV New Year's Gala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6443220376968384,
            "question": "Are there any other televised New Year's specials around the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5529363751411438,
            "question": "How does the CCTV New Year's Gala reflect Chinese culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of CCTV New Year's Gala is Category:New_Year's_television_specials.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1210_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other televised New Year's specials around the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1210_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the historical context of the CCTV New Year's Gala?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1210_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is the CCTV New Year's Gala popular?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1210_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1210_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1210_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1210_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1210_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1210_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1210_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1210_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1210_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1210_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1210_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that \"CCTV New Year's Gala\" is a category of \"New Year's television specials\". The documents mention that the CCTV New Year's Gala is an annual televised Chinese New Year celebrations, and a TV show that is broadcast on the eve of Chinese New Year, live on CCTV-1, and by satellite on other channels. This information is consistent with the concept of a new year's television special."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the CCTV New Year's Gala, including that it is an annual televised Chinese New Year celebration and a category of New Year's television specials. Therefore, the statement is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The CCTV New Year's Gala does not exclusively fall under the category of \"New Year's television specials.\" While it is broadcast on New Year's Eve and thematically related to the Chinese New Year, it also includes a wide variety of entertainment genres such as drama, dance, and song. Therefore, it encompasses a broader scope than just being classified as a \"New Year's television special.\"",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}